# **Greyce Bastos**

57, Bishops Court – Cambridge – UK

E-mail: <a href="mailto:greyce.amorim@yahoo.com.br">greyce.amorim@yahoo.com.br</a>
Phone: +44 77 09684293

LinkedIn: http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=92885656

Website: http://greyceamorim.github.io/ GitUser: greyceamorim

Date of Birth: 5th October 1986 Nationality: Brazilian Marital Status: Married

Visa Status: Family member of an EEA (No need sponsor)

I am an experienced IT professional with over 6 years of experience in development. My background are C#, ASP.NET, MVC, VB.Net, Jquery, JavaScript, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS and SQL Server database administration.

#### **Education**

#### MBA in Marketing (Incomplete)

02/2012 – 11/ 2012

Business School São Paulo - Laureate International Universities, São Paulo

## **Technology Analysis and Systems Development**

07/2004 - 07/2007

University of Mogi das Cruzes, São Paulo

## **Experiences abroad**

- Interchange in Ireland 06/2013 05/2014
- Interchange in Ireland 01/2013 02/2013

#### Work experience

#### Front End Developer

07/2015 - 11/2015

Stefanini: IT Outsourcing & Software Application Development - São Paulo, Brazil

• I have created the FrontEnd application for an intern product (Account Management for Banks) of Stefanini. And I have used HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, Ajax, Web Services, PostgreSQL, SVN, ReactJS, JavaScript ES6, JSON, REST, BOWER, GULP, JUNIT, MAVEN, Bootstrap and in some other applications I used Materialize.

### Leader Development Team Superabiz, São Paulo – Brazil

07/2014 - 05/2015

- I was responsible for leading a development time, deployment and customization the TOTVS Fluig Solution – that is a new and great platform in Brazil and it contains ECM (Enterprise Content Management), BPM (Business Process Management), WCM (Web Content Management), Social, Identity, Analytics and ESB (Enterprise Service Bus). The development and customization was developed with JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, HTML5, CSS3, Web Service, Rest and BPM Notation.
  - I was also responsible for:
- Requirements elicitation / process engineering.
- Development technical documentation.
- Conducting training for the users.

 Projects carried out for those companies (Afeet Group, ADESTE Group, Grafite Fairs and Teresa Perez Tourism)

## Au Pair/Nanny (Ireland)

09/2013 - 05/2014

• Experience with English language and other culture with the help of a host family. The experiences with kids were great for my auto development.

**IT Volunter** 07/2013 – 08/2013

Edge-Export, Dublin - Ireland

• I fixed the bugs in Edge-Export's system control using VBA for Excel Advanced.

# Software Analyst

03/2013 - 05/2013

Azix Informática, São Paulo - Brazil

- I participated of development of the Web Application of sanitation services registry, with capture, validation and standardization of field, rule checking address and all business rules defined by the customer. The service may include load data into operational bases of ERP, CRM with C#, ASP MVC, ASP.NET, DataLing, Jquery, SQL SERVER 2008.
- And also I have maintenance their olds web application in C# and SQL Server.

## **Software Analyst**

02/2011 -02/2013

Equipaindustria.com.br, São Paulo - Brazil

- I have participated of developing e-commerce customizable and easy to use for our customers; our customers can have their own e-commerce without having to understand programming. Fully customizable and user friendly using ASP MVC, C#, SQL Server.
- I have developed internal systems and websites with ASP.Net, C#, Jquery, Fluent NHibernate and SQL SERVER 2008.
- (ETL) Process DataBase (Excel, Txt) to our database with schedules in SQL Server.
- I also participated as internal quality auditor at the company Taquions (sub company of the Equipaindustria.com.br).

**Developer** 12/2006 – 02/2011

Página Viva CRM, São Paulo - Brazil

- I was responsible for maintenance and administration Database SQL Server 2000/2005.
- I also participated of development and maintenance of CRM systems for Nestlé, Bombril, Procter & Gamble using ColdFusion, HTML, Jquery e CSS and of systems integration using VB.NET, ASP.NET and SQL Server.
- And BI for marketing campaigns, generating reports to share information and business via Excel Advanced.
- Technologies used: Cold Fusion, Ajax, JavaScript, JQuery, VB.Net, ASP.Net, SQL Server 2000/2005, Excel VBA.

#### **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**

- Excellent Knowledge of: .NET, C#, VB.Net, Cold Fusion.
- Web Programming in ASP MVC 3, ASP.Net (Web Forms, Fluent NHibernate), JavaScript, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Jquery.
- Version control systems: TortoiseSVN, GitHub.
- Knowledge of modelling RUP, UML 2.0.
- Programming Concepts Layers + Web N, Web services, structured programming, object orientation, XML, XSL.
- Database SQL Server, PostgreSQL, MySQL (procedures, functions, views, triggers, DTS, SSIS, concepts transaction log, etc.).
- Technical requirements analysis, database optimization, development standards, and documentation.